There are so many good like deep like
low-level researchers and CTF players.
They would be amazing bug hunters if
they tried. Oh yeah. Yeah. 100%.
Best part of Viking when you can just
you know critical think
[Music]
right. Yeah dude.
So there are a lot of reasons why I love
Threat Locker. I talk about it from time
to time, but one of the reasons that's
really cool is that they don't talk down
to their users in their marketing
material, right? So let me let me give
you an example. There's this new product
they've released called Threat Locker
Web Control. Uh it it allows you to
simplify your environment by taking web
control like website categorization and
that sort of thing um and creating
policies for those categorizations and
then sort of building that into the
threat locker ecosystem so you don't
have to have a third party doing it.
Great simplicity. We love it. Right? But
as I'm reading through this page and I'm
listening to this little webinar
snippet, I'm sharing my screen on
YouTube by the way. Um there's this one
piece of marketing material that just
makes me smile. Right? that says our web
control does not rely on DNS to redirect
users to another website as that will
often cause certificate errors. Instead,
they will be redirected to a company
managed page with their instructions on
their options. And at the end, it
mentions this threat locker browser
extension that enhances the user
experience, making it super easy for
them to uh request permission to block
sites. So, I just I just freaking love
how they're like, "Yeah, you know, DNS,
it's cool, but it causes certificate
errors, so we're going to sort of work
around that." Right? They give you a
technical explanation of the
implementation, which is cool. And then
also they care about the UX, right? Um,
that's why they built the browser
extension to make it easy for their
users to uh get to the right spot and
know their options when a website that
they need to access is getting blocked.
And I'll try not to yap about it for too
long, but in this webinar here, they
also mention that um there's like
various types of categorization that is
done and that they're using machine
learning for that in in you know for
their main type of categorization, but
they also have a human go back and
remove some of those false positives and
they've already removed over 6,000 false
positives. Um and they've just launched
this product a couple months ago. So um
clearly they're doing a great job here.
Love the technical implementation. Love
that they're simplifying the ecosystem.
Way to go, Threat Locker as always. All
right, let's go back to the show. That's
it. Sup, hackers. We got a this weekend
bug bounty real quick and we got a
couple announcements from a couple
different places. We'll start with Yes,
We Hacks new program that went public,
Louis Vuitton. Now, if you guys are
following the live hacking event scene
at all, there was a pretty sick live
hacking event for Louis Vuitton that's
happened in the past couple years. Um,
and I was salty that I didn't make it to
that one. I would have loved to uh have
hacked on them because it's a cool
brand, right? Louis Vuitton. It's nice
to be able to say you've hacked Louis
Vuitton. Um and now it's public on Yes,
We Hack. Uh bounties are looks like uh
$100 for a low, mediums up to 600, highs
up to 1,800, and criticals up to 4K. And
that is in euros. Um so a little bit
bump there from USD. Um seems like
they're a pretty good program. Uh from
what I've heard, they're good to work
with. I wish we could get them to
release uh like some hacker exclusive
Louis Vuitton swag, but um I know that
they're really protective of their
brands. So, uh I don't know if I see
that happening anytime soon, but that
would be amazing. So, Yes, We Hack, I
know you're listening. You got to make
that happen. Um but if any of you guys
are interested, that program is now
public on Yes, We Hack. Um the other one
was something really, really scary
uh that came out of a Yes, We Hack bug
bounty program. Uh and that was CVE
202547934 which is a open
PGP.js signature and encryption uh
bypass here. Um very scary. Uh yeah they
essentially this affects inline
signatures and uh the signed and
encrypted messages. Um and I'll I'll
just go ahead and read from this thing
here. data uh detached signatures were
not affected. Um but in order to spoof
the attacker needs to create a single
valid message signature inline or
detached as well as plain text data that
was legitimately signed and then they
can construct an inline signed message
or sign encrypted message with any data
of the attacker's
choice. That one's bad. So, uh, yeah, I
actually when I saw the CVE come across
my my doc, I was like, uhoh, I got to
go, uh, update some code that I've
written. Um, and I did and we're fine.
But, um, this is an extremely impactful
vulnerability and is going to be used
both on the client side and the server
side because it affects open pgp.js. Um,
so you can see this in node apps or you
can see this in client side apps as
well. Um, the uh GitHub uh announcement
right here credits Yes, We Hacks uh
OpenPGP.js bug bounty program. And I
just wanted to shout out uh Eduardo at
the Coodian Labs team for finding that
because that's pretty sick. So, um if
you guys are assessing any like open
source apps and you know for sure
they're using open PGP, then this CV
would be a good one to try to get your
hands on the pock for. Um they did list
the uh let me see where they are. Yeah,
they did list the commits on GitHub that
uh they used to fix it. So should be
pretty easy to reverse the actual
vulnerability
itself. All right, that's what I had for
Yes, we hack. Moving over to uh hacker
one, we had a write up uh on a program
called dust and unfortunately this
wasn't a bug bounty. This was a a a VDP
but um the title of it was stored XSS
and file upload leads to privilege
escalation and full workspace takeover
and just kind of reading through this
the report is really well written and
really well done but this is exactly
what we've talked about which is these
you know just like web 3 AI also has um
web 2 problems right and this is just a
a a traditional um file upload uh
content type issue right uh that affects
this AI um platform. And so when you're
attacking AI, definitely, you know, make
sure you're listening to all of Rezo's
advice that he's talked about on the the
hacking series um and also on his uh
blog with the massive AI hacking
writeup, but also don't forget
your just basic W or web two
vulnerabilities, right? Because they
affect everything. Um all right, that's
all I had on the uh this week in Bug
Bounty for this week. So, let's get back
to the show. Peace.
I had some people over to my house
yesterday because whenever you talk to
your friends about being a like a hacker
they're like, "Oh my gosh, I want to
learn how to do that." So, every couple
months I'll run these like uh it's
probably like every two or three months
I'll run these little like house hacker
training things where I just kind of I
have a list of people that are like,
"Yeah, I want to try that. Yeah, I want
to try that." And I just send them all a
message right when I'm about to do this.
And um we just all gathered in my sun
room and I just cover a bunch of little
basic basic things and then we spend
like an hour, hour and a half looking at
HTTP requests and hacking targets and uh
and dude yesterday was like was one of
the best ones I've ever run cuz we found
two bugs on uh on Oh my goodness, that's
insane. I would have never expected to
actually pop a bug. I figured you would
start with like um I don't know DVMH or
something like that. um or DVWA. But
anyways, um yeah, I think in general
this is like really cool that you do
that. It makes me want to do it. And I
think that it probably saves people like
weeks of time. There are so many simple
questions you have at the beginning like
what does this box do at the top? You
know, like what exactly is the URL
versus the host header? you know, like
there's just so many like little small
things that you don't understand as a
beginner that take a lot of time to
slowly to pick up on that people don't
talk about that they can just ask you in
person like that. So, so here's the
recipe for that, man. This is what I
I've been kind of doing with people is
I'll bring them over. I'll say in
advance, you got to like your first
challenge is to get Kaido or Burp set up
on your computer, right? Yeah. And and
get the certificate thing susted. Okay.
And then, you know, when they arrive,
they've got that done typically. So,
good work. And then I I I spend very
little time talking about like most of
the time what I would do before is go
into like uh how HTTP works and stuff
like that. But at this point I just say
hey look you can inspect HTTP here. This
is the the way that everything
communicates. We need to look at the
path just the path and the body. Don't
worry about the headers right now. Yeah.
Just the path and the body of the
requests. Okay. and we're going to try
to find uh I I I give them a little lab
on IDORS and I give them a little ad uh
a lab on client side access controls,
right? And then after we've done that,
we pick a real app and we start we we
just start poking at it and uh and yeah,
dude, it was crazy because yesterday the
first the first attack vector that we
tried, it actually worked and I was
like, "Yeah, guys, guys, wait, wait,
wait, wait. This is not guys." Yeah,
this is not how this normally works.
Like
And and then later on we found another
one that that was uh definitely a valid
bone. But I I I just fear I've ruined
them a little bit. Yeah, you did. Yeah.
All the rest of us spent months finding
like informationals and things like I
promise it's a version leak here. You
shouldn't be telling your workers that
there's a version leak here. You know,
trying to justify little lame bugs.
That's so cool. Yeah. Yeah, man. It it
it's it's cool. And we normally try to
split it split the bounty evenly across
the group so that everybody gets like,
you know, a little hit of the wow, it
got paid sort of thing. Um, so yeah, I
do that for my friends that I know in
real life. Uh, so please, like, I can't
do it for everybody, guys. Please don't
DM on that. But, um, yeah, for the for
the people that I've I've met in real
life, they it's it's a pretty fun time.
And and I think as more advanced
hackers, right, like this is a really
fun little thing you can do for your
friends that are like, I want to be a
hacker, too. Yeah. Honestly, I I think
that people that feel the urge to DM you
about this should actually host it
because they're going to learn so much
by like walking someone through it. It
keeps you very focused, keeps you trying
things, and then you're basically, like
you said, you're like um showing people
what they think is really cool. So yeah.
Yeah, man. It was so hype. We were all
like freaking out when we found a
podcast. It was awesome, man. Yeah.
Yeah. And you've got that energy that's
in that's that's uh Wow, what's that
called? Uh whenever something is
contagious. Yeah, you have a very
contagious energy. So, I'm sure that
what's that word? When it's contagious.
Yes. Yeah. I was thinking some word like
enthusiastic or something. But anyways,
yeah. You want to jump to something
technical? Yeah, let's let's jump to the
technical content. Um you want to take
one first or should I? Yours is really
good. Talk talk to him about the super
base thing. Yeah, cool. I mean, I think
in general, uh so this is 100% a shout
out to Shell Sell Justin Reinhardt. I
did not find this but when he messaged
me I was like oh that's so genius
because I've tried to test superbase
related apps. Oh, so anyone who doesn't
know what Superbase is, basically it's
like a managed Postgress that has a
whole bunch of like default
functionality like arbback control and
all this and nearly every AI app these
days like you know new startups or if
you use like bolt new or vzero a lot of
them are using superbase under the hood
and they'll even like sometimes have a
button that's like enable superbase
integrate superbase like so it's baked
into so many of these new AI apps.
Anyways, their API calls for pulling
stuff back often use a format where it's
like equals eq dot and then like a uyu
ID and then that will fetch some object.
So it might be a user object, it might
be a conversation object, it might be
whatever you name it, right? And I had
tried putting in other UU IDs from other
places in the app like you know crosser
testing and that sort of thing and if
they have role access turned on it
doesn't work. And so um you know I found
like where role level security is
disabled and I've reported that to some
some people but um one thing that I for
some reason had never thought to try
that Justin found which is amazing is
just doing LT so less than or GT greater
than and then putting in a UU ID that's
like like GT dot and then all all zero
UU ID or LT do all 999's UU ID right um
actually weird that it processes it like
that because it's like UU IDs aren't
Yeah, they're not numeric in that way.
Yeah. Okay. So, I'm I'm I'm gonna share
my screen really quick. I was trying to
find something that has that that syntax
in it, and I I was googling around and
this is the only thing I could I could
find that had it. Um but this is a a a
um a GitHub discussion, and you can see
it right here. This is what you're
talking about, right? Yep. That's
exactly it. It's It's always like a
select star, too, for some reason. It's
That's a weird format, man. I've never
seen anything like that. Yeah. Um, yeah.
And then here we go. Right. This is the
actual format right here. EQ dot. So he
changed this to like less than or you
know zeroed out the whole UU ID and then
did greater than or something like that.
And it and it processed the UU IDs as a
numeric entity. Yeah, it's always looks
super juicy because I mean look at the
end. It looks like you're just like
injecting straight into a query. And
they always look that way. I don't know
if that's just by design. Um, in general
it is usually sort of secure-ish. I
found plenty where it's not. But
anyways, really interesting and a very
quick tip for people to go find some
bugs in these new AI. That's I would
definitely have not have thought that
that would that you could do like a less
than or greater than a UU ID. So, that's
got to be a weird quirk to superbase.
Yeah. Um or maybe I'm off on that, you
know. Hit up the hashtag corrections
channel on on uh on the critical
thinking discord if you've got more info
on on what I'm missing about that. Um
but yeah, that's definitely definitely a
cool one. Um, all right. Let me I'll
I'll I'll share this next one here. Um,
guys, there there are a couple people
out there that whenever they tweet, you
should just be paying attention, okay?
And and lately, Jorian has become that
for me. Like, he he really has just been
dropping stuff left and right. Um, that
is really impactful. Um, Slanzer has has
become that lately, you know, like there
there are a couple people that weren't
really on my radar as much besides the
past couple months and they're just
crushing it. Zero is another that
researcher uh Z Hero O. But anyway, um
here's a latest post by Dorian that I
that came up in my uh in my
notifications because I have not
notifications turned on for for this
guy. And um it's a really interesting
thing that he has here, which is uh
there's a fun trick to detect when
actions like shortcuts or clicks are
happening in a cross origin iframe,
which is not something that you normally
are able to do very well. Um and
something that I've needed in past
exploits to detect when a click has
occurred inside of an iframe. Um and the
way because you need to update something
like you need to update what's drawn on
the screen or something. Yeah, exactly.
You know, cuz if you're clickjacking or
something like that, right? like you
it's sometimes helpful to understand
whether they've clicked on in the button
you know in that in that iframe so that
you can maybe send a post message or or
do something you know uh to to
manipulate the page or if you need to
harvest multiple clicks then you can
change your offset right on the on the
page uh to to to click on a different
button this next time or something like
that. Um and this trick that he has here
is really interesting. It uses navigator
do useract activation isactive and it
checks it you know on an interval of 0
milliseconds. So it's just constantly
checking it and then as soon as a a a
user activation is is triggered. So on
the top level page uh apparently this
can also detect clicks in the in the
bottom level page. It consumes that user
activation by doing a window.open which
consumes the uh the user activation and
then instantly closes it. So it's boom
boom and then now that page is not
selected again. So the user, you know,
if they want to if they want to click on
something again, it will trigger that
user activation call once again. And
then you can repeat the process. So it
it's a way for you to constantly like
harvest a change to the user activation
state and then reset it uh so that it it
you can detect it again. Very very smart
technique. Definitely going to be using
that in some of my client side exploits
in the future. I've noticed that this
comes from Jorian quote tweeting a
person named Atomic Bite where where
they somehow do clipjacking where like
you can get owned by copying. That's
like really unique. I need to go in and
read this. Yeah, let me Yeah, exactly.
It is. That's another one lately um
that's been crazy. So, let me let me go
to this article. I I I read through this
and here's the PC on corrected me on
pronunciation. I think it's Jol. Jal.
Okay. Well, so sorry, dude. We We do our
best. for podcasters, you know, like
it's difficult. But um check out this PC
dude. So he he past it in here and he
says just hold down control ACV and then
he grabs all of this information from
this domain, right? So you can embed a
page and then there's like you just
press control arr C selects everything
on the page and then the attacker can
using this click dete or this uh event
detection
can you know then focus force focus onto
a a text area and then when they press
controlV it paste that content into the
text area. Y uh and so it's it's a very
sneaky way to do like
cross-sight hijacking of information.
And I've actually seen um uh some
research by Matan Bear that is also
really really cool on this that I'm
going to have him come on and talk about
at some point uh where you can do
something very similar. Um so yeah, I
got to write that down because uh people
want more from the researchers. Come on,
Justin. I know. I know. And I and
they've been finding cool stuff. We just
haven't done the thing. Yeah. Published
it. So, there's going to be more coming
from that soon if I can. The phrase is
what gets measured gets managed. So, you
need to like say we're going to release
one thing per month or something. Yeah.
Yeah, dude. Yeah. But it's it's
difficult, right? And that kind of flows
into our topic for later where it's like
um talking about how to balance the
opportunities that you get when you're a
full-time bug bounty hunter and like the
reason that you maybe became a full-time
bug bounty hunter in the first place,
which is to live a life of full
flexibility, right? So anyway, we'll get
to that, but let's let's uh let's pound
out the rest of this technical content
first. Cool. Yeah, let's go super
technical first and then that way
throughout the episode we slowly get
less technical. But um the the thread I
wanted to share was um and mostly it's
just a user to follow. But let me share
my screen. It is his name is Wyatt
Walls, but um he's kind of been around
the prompt injection space a little bit.
I don't know them other than you know
following them on X share screen.
Um hopefully is this uh let's see uh we
are going to delete my messages. Left
hand draft. Sorry for uh yepand draft.
Sorry to the editors. Um, anyways, the
they basically did really well on the
Grey Swan um like hacker hacker prompt
challenge or whatever. I think you
people probably saw me tweet about it or
whatever. Grey Swan is a company that
makes like models called Signet and
they're like pretty resilient to prompt
injection. Anyways, um they ran a
challenge where you could earn money and
stuff and um the they're you know Wyatt
is now allowed to tweet about it. And so
he basically breaks down in this thread
which we'll share um all like a bunch of
different prompt injection payloads
where they're trying to get um an email
agent to do malicious actions. And
that's really useful and beneficial
because one agents are going to keep
cropping up. too, as we'll talk about in
just a second with Google IO, Google is
obviously cares deeply about this stuff
and pays well and their Gemini is now
going to basically be able to access
your emails from like all over the
place. Like look through your docs, look
through your emails, like yeah, I've got
a lot to say about Google IO in just a
second, but anyways, all that to say,
this is a really good thread on prompt
injection payloads and the ways that you
could weaponize or get malicious actions
out of like an email agent. So, people
should just look at this. I don't want
to um beat a dead horse about it. And I
also know that we're constrained on time
today, but you should follow you should
follow uh this person and also if you're
interested in AI security and also um
potentially, you know, use these
payloads to test Google or other
companies that have big bug money
programs. So, so speaking of like
programs that have, you know, that you
need to put a lot of payloads through
and stuff like that, are you able to
talk about the thing you showed me right
before this uh podcast or does that need
to wait a little bit? No, I think it's
fine. I I don't mind to share. I don't I
don't think that I'm doing anything
there that um one it's people to um yeah
one if people can replicate it that's
great if they can't that's not that's
fine too but um anyways I have basically
been doing AI safety testing for a major
major model provider since it's a
private program I won't mention it but
I'm sure most people saw it they tweeted
about it actually yeah I can just say it
since they tweeted about it basically
has an AI safety challenge going on and
anyone who applies can do it so you
should go apply it's really cool but the
way it works is they've got some um
malicious prompts that if you can get
the model to respond to then you get a
bounty and they then will submit your
same payload with their with their
hidden request that they want to see if
it'll pass on the back end and if it
also passes those you get an even bigger
bounty. So that's really cool but I
wrote a system that is kind of similar
to Hadex's system. I assume his is
better. He's been cranking on it for
longer and it's similar to what this
company that I'm an adviser for called
Splicks or SPLX made internally that
they use for their stuff. Basically, um,
when it comes to making a prompt
payload, as you and I discussed on the
Google episode, like there's always like
a goal or, you know, you're trying to do
something. So, you have to have the
model respond in a certain way and then
often you'll need to like bypass
guardrails and sometimes you do that
through through obuscation things. And
so um I know whenever Hadex described
his he described it as like a tactic or
like a goal and then like a technique
like but through this form of injection
or through this form of storytelling or
whatever and then the offuscation at the
end which is like B 64 encoded or
invisible unicoded tags or whatever. Um
and that's cool but I always thought
like man that's still you selecting all
three items and generating and then
copying and pasting the payload blah
blah blah. I needed that to be way more
automated. So when I built mine I
basically it's like two-step. The first
step is it iterates over every uh attack
tactic that I could come up with. I'm
sure there are a lot more. I need to
refine those prompts, but every attack
tactic and then every offuscation tactic
that I could come up with. And then I
put in a custom goal. And then when I
hit run, it it does every permutation of
the tactic and the offuscation payload.
All of that goes to a um prompt writer.
And so I'm using Sonic 37 for my prompt
writer because um Anthropic has in their
console, if people don't know this, it's
like pretty high value, high utility.
Basically, if you're designing some sort
of AI app um and you want to improve
your prompt inside of Anthropic's
console, like in the workbench, I think
is what it's called. You can have it
write a prompt for your app. And it's
really good. And so I was like, hm, so I
I'll probably have this thing write the
prompts. So, it takes my goal, it takes
my tactic that I want to use to try to
get the model to respond unsafeely, and
it takes my offuscation payload, and it
gives that to the prompt writer, which
is Sonnet 37. It outputs the the prompt
that then the malicious prompt that then
tries to get this new model they're
testing to respond in an unsafe fashion.
So, it's kind of like a thing, dude.
Yeah. Well, that's actually one thing
that makes it really hard. So, actually,
this is a really good pro tip for
anybody who's out there developing apps
that deal with prompt injection or
jailbreaks. If you want to write code
like let's say you're using cursor and a
part of your app is a prompt or a
jailbreak. One thing that gets confusing
is the agent now is influenced by that.
So it's really hard to write a code
around that because it's like the model
has to like hold this metastate in its
mind and like not get confused by all
these jailbreak payloads as it's trying
to write code over here. And so the way
that I have kind of fixed that or solved
that, so this is the pro tip for
everybody is basically template all
those out into a file that you don't
give access to the model and then just
you like let it have those variable
names or those enumes or whatever and so
it can use those enums in the process of
writing its code but it can't see those
payloads and then you can edit those
payloads or just include that when
you're executing the the app at runtime
but don't include that in the context
because all of those payloads will
confuse it. I actually do that a lot
with shift like when we're working on
shift and stuff because those payloads
can confuse it as well. Yeah. Yeah. Wow.
That's that's a lot of Yeah, that is a
lot for it to keep straight, I'm sure.
But it's interesting that you're using
AI to build a prompt to hack AI. I feel
like they would deny I feel like you
might run into denials on the prompt.
You're exactly right. So, I was worried
about that and for some reason Sonic
37's fine with it. Yeah, I I I do agree
with you. I thought I would have to like
convert to Groc or something that's
like, you know, less safe. that's like
doesn't refuse at all, but I haven't had
to yet. So, yeah, that's funny. Croc
just doesn't refuse anything. Groc has
no refusals. Yeah, you can you can
convince Grock to do whatever you want.
That's really smart. So, it's good for
hacking. Nice. All right, next on the
list, uh I just wanted to give a shout
out to the Whiz team. I just went on
their their podcast um and did an
episode with them. Lots of fun. So,
check out their uh the podcast Crying
Out. How is that episode performing?
Have they told you any stats or metrics?
I haven't checked it out, actually. I'll
have to I'll have to go see. Uh
definitely, you know, go check it out,
guys, if you want more more content. Uh
I I I you know, you you've been saying
for a while, Joseph, that we should do
like a interview of me, cuz most of the
time I'm on here interviewing people and
stuff like that. And so Crying Out Lou
Cloud is kind of a version of that. And
they spend a lot of time, they actually
really did their research on me. They're
like, "So you play volleyball, right? So
you do jiu-jitsu, right?" And I'm like,
"So when you were six and a half years
old and you fell off the stoop and you
hit How was that?" Gez, they got some
like serious uh recon going on over
there. Like that makes that makes
interviews great though. I'm a huge fan
of uh podcasts and the one of my
favorites is Conversations with Tyler.
Tyler Cowen is just a polymath about
everything and interviews experts on
everything and he reads anything they've
ever written even if it's like multiple
books and digs deep and those always
make for some of the best questions.
Yeah. Yeah. So it was a great interview.
So, we'll we'll link it uh in the
description, but I just wanted to also
shout out them because they their
research team won Pone to Own, which is
a huge accomplishment. Um, and that's
something that we've kind of been I've
been trying a little bit to to get
people from pone to own on the podcast.
We had Cynology on and and um uh Sharon
Brisenov that that did uh some pone to
own stuff. So, I definitely want to get
more people from the pone to own space
onto the podcast and talk to them. So,
I'm going to send out some feelers uh to
some of the people that that performed
well at this phone to own and see if we
can get more people own because I think
it is a really different world than the
normal, you know, web bug bounty world.
And I think I would like to um try to
cross that gap a little bit. Um I think
that'd be so many good um like deep like
low-level researchers and CTF players.
They would be amazing bug hunters if
they tried. Oh yeah. Yeah. 100%.
Speaking of little mini shout out, I um
Jacobe, you know, a lot of people might
um know know him from some of his like
Microsoft research and stuff. He has
been like leaning into Bug Bounty and
tweeting a lot about it. And I just love
it so much because like I think he's a
you know, a researcher and like a
technical person who's like knows a lot
about Microsoft products and has never
really done Bug Bounty and like within a
week was already finding bugs on
Microsoft. And so um yeah, dude, what's
his what's his handle? Do you know? I
think it's I am Jacobe. I am Jacobe.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh,
okay. Yeah. For some reason, I
always I I I'd never heard anybody say
that name out loud. Did you say Jacobe
or something? Jacobe. That's what I was
thinking it was. And when you said
Jacobe, I was like, the freak is that?
Yeah. No, I saw that saying wrong. I
don't know. But so, uh, so yeah,
definitely like to see people pivoting
into that space a little bit. Um, all
right. Uh, and then this was the other
one that we wanted to talk about, uh,
was once again, uh, our boy Gareth
Hayes, uh, Portugu Research pointed
something out that was really cool that
actually originally came from, uh, Simon
Peters. Um, and this is that actually a
new XSS vector with, uh, with the image
tag. Um, and it no longer requires the
source property. Image
taggs are so hot. these days. Image
image related things, right? Yes, it is,
dude. Speaking of Oh, to close the loop
on that. They patched your your leak.
Ah, shoot. They did patch it, man.
Freaking June Kokatu, man. I swear this
guy I should not have tagged him, but uh
yeah, you know, they they actually
turned it around much faster than I
expected. I was expecting a year plus,
you know, deprecation time on that, but
I guess they just said this has got to
be closed up now. And and it makes sense
cuz it's that's like the referral policy
being able to be bypassed is pretty bad.
Yet oneclick ATO's I saw somebody like
Max or whatever got paid twice. So yeah,
I think like yeah, over the course of
over what I've seen in the critical
thinking community, I saw 15 plus ATO's
get get paid out with that bug. Like it
was crazy. Yeah. Okay. Anyway, back to
this. This is not related to refer
policy or leaks or anything like that. I
thought I thought it was interesting and
funny that they were both image related.
So yeah, tell us how this works. So, so
Gareth, you know, tweeted out just a
tweet that says um image source set
equals 1, on error equals alert one. And
this is interesting because typically
the source parameter was required for
images, image based exploits in the
past. The on error and the onload won't
work unless you have a source um
attribute. Uh but now you can actually
get it to trigger uh with source set. So
if there's something looking for source
equals or something like that or you're
having some problem there, you can use
source set equals 1. Um, and that will
also trigger the on error uh for an
image tag. And then the guy that he was
quote tweeting on this, Simon, said
actually you can trigger it without even
having any other attributes. So just
image on error equals alert one. Um, if
you wrap it in a source tag uh that has
source set equal to one. Oh,
interesting. Um, which I was really
confused about, but I I tried it in my
browser and it worked. So, um, yeah,
it's just those little niche things you
want to know about when you're in these
exploitation scenarios where, you know,
maybe you're going up for some some
weird W or something that really does
not like the source attribute on an
image or something. Um, the source set
could could get you past it. Sweet.
Yeah, pretty solid. Let's use the next
three minutes to cover any other news
and then we'll save the last 15 for our
kind of discussion. Okay. Yeah, that
sounds good, man. Um, I wanted to Do you
want me to Are you more interested in
hearing about Google IO since you didn't
pay attent tune in or the coding agent
stuff? I'll just I'll wrap it all in one
quick thing. Do it. Do it. Wrap it. Cuz
I'd like to hear about those. Yeah.
Yeah. So crazy. In the last like three
or four days, we'll just call it the
last week, but I think it's really been
the last three or four days, we've seen
Codeex be released from OpenAI, which is
like basically their hacking or their
coding agent. So you can even apparently
like use it from your phone. The
majority of these coding a coding agents
I think are in like the $200 a month
price tier, but they're really good.
Like um I've seen a lot of people who
are very technical talk about how
impressed they are with it. But anyways,
you can basically just like you just
connect up your GitHub and you choose
like a branch and you just like give it
a prompt and it goes and it'll do a PR
and then submit the PR and it happens
through your O. So it kind of looks like
you did it too, which is interesting.
But you can basically go in and then
review the PR and just approve it or
deny it. And so you can just spin up
hundred of these, right? as long as you
have the time to review the PRs, just
spin them up for whatever features you
want to add to your app and then just
like approve, deny it, and um kind of
have like automated Yeah. Yeah, dude. I
don't know. I mean, cursor like even
with cursor currently, like it it
it does implement features pretty well,
but it definitely needs to be tweaked
when things are more complex. And I
think the real crazy thing that's going
to happen with these things is when it
can actually validate that it wrote the
code correctly. So you can give it a
scenario where it's like all right come
to this web page click this button enter
this text and uh this object should be
added to the page and there's no doubt
that that's possible now with through
things like Selenium and browser use and
MCP servers like there's no doubt that
that's possible but yeah I haven't seen
it like done really well yet. Yeah, it
needs to be able to validate that it
wrote the code correctly, you know, like
and and then if it can then it's like,
oh, this is sick. Like could you imagine
just just like essentially just writing
in plain English test cases or
essentially writing software would then
get reduced to like user requirements,
right? Right. as a you know if anybody's
ever done like the uh the user stories
or whatever it's like as a user I want
to do you know XYZ and and then you just
write those and you give it to the AI
and the AI will like write the code
check that it did the thing correctly
and then dude no I think it's I think
it's coming yeah so multiple companies
release stuff like that Google's is
called Jules Julesgoo and June
and it was a part of their Google IO
release which released a ton of crazy
stuff they have they have glasses
finally you like Google Glass or we
started it. This is kind of closing the
loop on it that are fully multimodal
where they can it can see the world. You
can talk about your world. You can be
like where did I leave my coffee cup or
whatever and it overlays it on the
glasses and they they like are pretty
small form factor like they looked
pretty normal to me on stage. M yeah, I
had I I did see that and I was and I and
I think they're doing it more correctly
this time where where like it actually
is powered by your phone and the thing
on your glasses is just, you know,
batteries and and you know, input,
right? And then everything gets powered
from the, you know, phone in your
pocket. I think that makes way more
sense. Yeah. Yeah. This still like I
finally got my Meta Abands hooked up to
my new phone. For some reason, I wasn't
using them for months because I tried to
switch it and it didn't work and I
eventually did it and it's such a game
changer. It's so nice. Um, but anyways,
they also released the craziest video
generation I've ever seen. Have you seen
any of these videos? What is that? V3 or
something like that? Is that Have you
seen it with audio? No, but I freaking
saw it in the code when we were hacking
in Tokyo before it got released. I was
like, V3. That's That's kind of crazy.
What is that? And then I couldn't get it
to like work. It is insane. Like you
need to as soon as we hang up the call,
go look at it. Like it can basically do
a full video for you of whatever you
want and include audio and if when
people are speaking like their mouth
moves perfectly with the it's insane.
Like somebody generated like a guy
rapping about VO3 and it like just looks
perfect. Like you could convince me it's
real. So dude it's crazy. We're doing
the podcast right now with V3.
Yeah. No no I'm just kidding. I'm
kidding. I've seen a lot of people. It's
so good though. I've seen a lot of
people tweeting videos and saying like
can't believe this is AI generated. And
I I don't think it is. I think they're
just like posting like Rick like like
they're like like the Rick Ashley Rick
roll, but I legitimately can't tell
because it's overfit. You know how some
of the image models would like output
like Disney characters that look exactly
like Disney characters? Yeah. And you
could be convinced it was a screenshot
from one of the movies. That's how
that's how overfitit V3 is. So if you
have it make like copyright video of
like, you know, Rick Ashley, it looks
exactly like it. So you can't actually
tell if it's a generator or it's like
actually scraping from the video. So
yeah, we're entering that weird uncanny
valley. Yeah, that's that gets a little
bit that let's get gets a little bit
whack for sure. We will we will be on
this pod doing things live. I was
telling Richard that uh it would be
really cool if like if I like fumbled
over my words during a ad read or like
if I need, you know, needed to bleep
something out instead of bleeping it,
you know, it just seamlessly deleted it.
You know, I was
thinking very soon. I think it's 100%
possible with video editing and all
that. So anyways, oh we went a little
over time. But anyways, my whole point
was and I posted this in the critical
thinkers chat was like Google releases
10 products, go forth and hack, right? I
think it's like really cool that stuff
like that can happen and companies are
releasing stuff so fast. They are
cranking stuff out. So there's bugs
there for sure 100%. Um, all right. So,
I guess you and I were kind of talking
about what we wanted to do with this
episode beforehand, and I kind of wanted
to end this with a little bit of a chat
about full-time bug bounty because, you
know, you've been doing full-time bug
bounty for how long now? Five months.
February, March, April, May. Yeah. For
four months. Four months. Yeah. So, and
and I know that you and I have both had
this experience where it's like we we
become full-time book bounty hunters for
the purpose of living our life with
flexibility, right? And and you know, to
be honest, the the money part of
full-time Buck Bounty is great, too. And
I think I would I think it would be
possible for me to get a job outside of
Bug Bounty that pays more than I make in
Buck Bounty, for sure. But it would be a
little bit of a struggle. Um, and the
the major game changer with Bug Bounty
is that you have complete flexibility,
but that complete flexibility can kind
of I don't know, it affects your your
your full-time bug bounty vibe, right?
You're I feel like I'm not doing that
much bug bounty even though I'm
full-time bug. I definitely feel that
way. You know who who does a good job of
it? Douglas. Like he's he's full-time
and he'll very frequently be like, "Yep,
I'm on my fiveday streak. Five bugs five
days in a row or whatever." Um, dang,
dude. So maybe it's worth asking him.
But yeah, I so I guess your question is
kind of like how has that been for me?
Yeah. Yeah, that's what I'm asking.
Thanks. No, you're fine. Yeah, I think
that I thought that you were building
there. Yeah. So I think that um like you
said, being a Let's just start at the
beginning. I was a full-time employee. I
I like loved Bug Bounty so much. I
actually um there's a a misconception to
kind of clear up here. Um, I was like
considering going full-time bug bounty
when I was a full-time employee. But
there were some people who were like,
"What if it takes a joy away from it for
you?" Like you like it so much. What if
when you're doing it full-time, you
don't enjoy it as much? Yeah. I think
that that's just the human brain playing
tricks on people. I think that's like
saying, "Hey, what if you make too much
money? What what if what if you got too
buff?" You know, like there are people
who lose Dude, this is a really common
Do you know about this this stereotype?
There are a lot of people who are like,
I don't want to lift weights because I
don't want to get too big. It's like,
yeah, well, guess what? You won't do
that. And if you do, you just not work
out for a few months and you'll be small
again. It's like uh it's not like no one
is going to accidentally get too big. No
one's gonna accidentally make too much
money. And I think that's the same way
here. It's like if you really love
something, I think doing slightly more
of it. Um especially where you have a
fallback plan where anyone who's a top
bug hunter can go get a job pretty
easily. Like we all have these like big
safety nets. Those of us who like have
found plenty of bugs. So I I say all
that to say like um when I left I was
doing it to do more bug bounty and
you're right it has been kind of
paradoxical in the sense that I like am
doing more but it's not a lot more. So I
think the real win is and I know you
asked me about this before we started
rolling that what it does unlock is all
of the other things that were like maybe
bouncing around in your head or other
things that you wanted to do. So, I have
a lot of ideas every day, like they just
pop into my head, whether it's business
ideas or whether it's research ideas,
and I was never able to pursue them. I
don't know if that's true for you or
like how that's been for you. I if I had
to guess, critical thinking kind of was
that for you and and and maybe the
things you've done with critical
thinking. Exactly. Yeah, you're right.
100%. And so I think if you if you are
going to go full-time bug bounty and
like to become a full-time bug bounty
hunter and um you know you're just like
you know looking for reasons to do it
you know we're obviously big fans of it.
I think that that's a big thing you
could potentially unlock is instead of
it being your one hobby or your big
hobby outside of work, now when it
becomes the main thing, you have this
freedom to do other stuff that you love,
which for me has been like doing
advisorships, doing critical thinking,
doing doing just independent research or
like AI stuff. What What has it been for
you, Justin? What does your life outside
of fulltime look like? Like you said,
you're not doing that much. What's it
filled with? Yeah. Well, I mean, like I
think here's the other thing about this
is like we we make this decision to get
the freedom, right? And then I think a
piece of longevity for being a full-time
Bani hunter is living in that freedom,
right? And I think um you know, JRock
posted in the the accountability uh you
know, for the full-time hunters guild
and the accountability channel. He was
saying, you know, hey, it's I've I
crushed it for the first like however
many months of this year and I've just
been chilling for the past four weeks,
you know, and I'm like, hell yeah, dude.
That's what you got to do, you know. And
and I I I saw him when I was at
NorthStech in uh in Canada and I hung
out with him for a bit. Super nice
place, by the way. He's got a he's got a
great house and thank you for being a
great host, JRock. I know you listen to
these episodes. Um but he was saying,
you know, that that that's and I think
he was very wise that that is a very key
part of longevity in bug bounty as well,
right? Is like you can burn out really
easily. So live in that freedom that you
optimized for. And it doesn't
necessarily mean you are going to be
spending, you know, your 8 hours a day
even hacking um where where you might
want to be able to do other things like
go play tennis at 11:00 a.m. on a
Tuesday, you know, like and uh and
that's just a part of living that
lifestyle. Dude, speaking of living in
it and just sitting in it. Yeah. I think
this was mentioned on the Chris
Williamson podcast, like the one the
most recent one he released if anybody
wants to go look at that. But it's also
something that's been on my mind and
it's something you mentioned. So, I feel
like this is like sometimes I call this
obviously obviously I'm a Christian. I
sometimes call this like God connecting
the dots, but you know, maybe it's just
a theme for some people, right? But I
think there's a theme here that everyone
needs to grasp on to, which is just
being grateful and like sitting in your
wins. So, Chris Williamson was saying
that like for motivated people, they
don't sit in their wins, right? It's
like they set some goal, they get it,
and it's like the next day they're
working on the next thing. I think when
you mentioned this earlier, you
mentioned it in the context of Kaido,
like just being an adviser for Kaido.
like you've just been really enjoying it
and you've been just thinking about
that. I don't think we just I don't
think we think about the joy that our
hobbies or our interests bring us very
often and like I want to do that a lot
more. Like we need to do that, man.
Yeah. I think anyone who's a critical
thinker or in the guild like they are at
the top of the coolest industry with the
coolest skill set that humans have ever
had. Like I think the hacking is just
like at least for us, for our type of
people, for people with our brain, like
it really is extremely cool and it's so
easy to lose sight of the fact that we
get to do something that we find so fun
and awesome. And so yeah, I think if
you're listening to this and you do bug
bounty, even if you're not making a
killing and you're just like making a
little bit of side hustle money or
you're struggling to find a bug, like
just remember like what it was like when
you wanted to be a hacker, when you
wanted to know how to hack, you know? I
think that um I want to take some time
and chill in that. Sit in that.
Appreciate that. Right. Yeah. I'm not
saying like let your foot off the gas,
but like when you're walking to the
bathroom, when you're in the car
driving, when you're about to go to
sleep at night, like just be like, "Man,
I've got it so good." Like this is
really cool. I'm so thankful I get to do
this. Yeah. Yeah. Totally, man. I think
that's a I think that's a great
reminder. Um and I think it's
interesting because there is a little
bit of a juosition on that, right? It's
like I think that probably if you want
to be, you know, and you actually had a
a really interesting tweet about this
the other day. If you really want to be
like the top the top the top the top the
top the top, you know, then, you know,
maybe you need to keep pushing pushing
pushing pushing. Um, and a lot of people
do if they especially if they really
love it. But I also think it's nice to
to like especially if you get maybe top
10% or whatever, right? to just like
enjoy that and and sit in it and you
know I don't know do you know what I'm
saying? Relish relish that experience.
Yeah. 1000%. I mean I think like a lot
of people who have succeeded have
succeeded because of their relentless
grind but I think that having that
reminder Naval or someone else there's a
lot of um you know big people
productivity people who mentioned this
like what we're doing is a is both a
means to an end and it's sometimes the
end itself like hacking like having fun
hacking is the end for me in some ways
like it's why I left my job because I
love it like and I think like if you if
the the means to the end is hacking Um,
then when you're making enough money to
sustain the lifestyle that you and your
family want, like you have kind of
reached that point that you are working
towards, don't constantly let your
monkey brain make you discontent because
you kept moving the goalpost. Like it's
okay to move the goalpost and to get
excited about it, but don't let yourself
be unhappy because of that. Nal does
have a really famous quote if you all
haven't heard it, but um it's um
uh it's like the promise you I'm I'm
gonna forget it. Do you know the one I'm
talking about? It's like, no. Oh, yeah.
Wanting. Wanting is the is the promise
you make to yourself to be discontent
until you get what you want.
It's so like you're basically saying,
you know, by wanting something like, oh,
I'm going to be discontent until I have
this thing or slightly discontent until
I have this thing, right? And so it's
like make sure that you don't keep
wanting. Desire is a contract you make
with yourself to be unhappy until you
get what you want. Yeah. And so I think
like Yeah. I mean, you know, I I believe
that, you know, there's a deeper level
of satisfaction that comes from
objective truth and other things, but I
think in general, a lot of people do um
they don't they don't they haven't
really thought about what they want, and
so they're just always going for more
when really they may have already
arrived at where they wanted to get. And
so, I c I certainly fall into that trap
from time to time. So, all right, man. I
think that's a wrap on this episode.
Yeah, let's end it with that. Yeah, I
love it. Peace. Hope you all enjoy it.
See you. And that's a wrap on this
episode of Critical Thinking. Thanks so
much for watching to the end, y'all. If
you want more critical thinking content,
uh, or if you want to support the show,
head over to
ctbb.show/isord. You can hop in the
community. There's lots of great
highlevel hacking discussion happening
there on top of master classes,
hackalongs, exclusive content, and a
full-time hunters guild if you're a
full-time hunter. It's a great time.
Trust me. All right, I'll see you there.